I write love songs in the morning
I write love songs in the day
I'll sing to you tomorrow
If I make it through today
I've been holding out for you baby
My arms a solid arc
Tell me you don't believe it
Life's gone and fucked me up
So I'll say it loud
You bring me to higher ground
See my mother in the kitchen
Her daughter by the door
And you, baby, were in the backcountry
Our baby on the floor
I'm a thousand different women
Dressed in shades of red
We won't win this race we're in
just like I always said
But love, you know just how
To bring me to higher ground
I sing love songs in the morning
I sing love songs in the day
I sing love songs on the subway, baby
Just to tell you I'm okay
Oh I'll sing it loud
You bring me to higher ground